Guide to the Graduate School of Political Management political advertisement videocassette collection, 1970-2005 MS2241.UA
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Graduate School of Political Management political advertisement videocassette collection
1970-2005
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
MS2241.UA
19 Linear Feet
This collection contains video cassettes used for educational purposes in GSPM classes. The videos contain political advertisements; local and national news reports and other broadcast programming related to politics; educational programs including forums, panels, lectures, and series; speeches, debates and political conventions; and political movies and documentaries. They range in date from 1970-2005 with some videos undated. The bulk of the collection materials cover 1988-1998.
Box UP0005
Box UP0002
Box UP0001
Box UP0004
Box UP0003
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the Graduate School of Political Management, 2007(Accession 2007.082)
Historical or Biographical Note
The Graduate School of Political Management, GSPM, part of The George Washington University in Washington, D.C., is the nation's first school for professional politics. Its mission is to "improve politics by educating its students and professionals in the tools, principles and values of participatory democracy, preparing them for careers and ethical and effective advocates and leaders at the international, national and local levels."
In 1986, Neil Fabricant, a lawyer from New York City and former Legislative Director of the New York Civil Liberties Union, proposed the creation of a dedicated school to nurture the development of the profession of politics. The Graduate School of Political Management was founded in September 1987 with 24 students. It was chartered by the New York State Board of Regents and operated as an independent graduate school on the Manhattan campus of Baruch College. Christopher Arterton was named Dean of the School. In September 1991, the School opened a degree program on The George Washington University campus. GSPM was acquired by the University in July 1995 and made a component of its Columbian School of Arts and Sciences.
The School offers Master of Professional Studies degrees in Political Management, Legislative Affairs and Strategic Public Relations, and graduate certificates in PACs and Political Management and Public Relations.
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains video cassettes used for educational purposes in GSPM classes. The videos contain political advertisements; local and national news reports and other broadcast programming related to politics; educational programs including forums, panels, lectures, and series; speeches, debates and political conventions; and political movies and documentaries. They range in date from 1970-2005 with some videos undated. The bulk of the collection materials cover 1988-1998.
This collection is a valuable historical record of television coverage of past elections, including candidate advertisements; news coverage; broadcasted debates, speeches and conventions; and interest group advertisements. This collection also provides a wealth of information on the process of creating effective political advertisements; the political process, including the political profession; and social issues relevant to elections or the political process.
This collection was donated by the Graduate School of Political Management in 2007.
Collection Organization
Organized into five series: Political advertisements; Broadcast programming; Political education; Speeches and debates; and Movies and documentaries.
Advertising; Politics and government; George Washington University. Graduate School of Political Management
- Political advertisements, 1970-2002; MS2241 Series 1; 10.5 Linear feet
  Scope and Contents note
  The videos of this series include political advertisements. They range in date from 1970-2002 with some undated videos. The bulk of the series covers 1990-1998, with particular emphasis on election years. The majority of the videos in this series contain advertisements for individual candidates that were aired on television. Other videos contain compilations of advertisements produced by political advertising companies for promotional purposes; advertisements produced by political parties and interest groups; and advertisements for political services. Advertisements cover some local, as well as state and national elections.
  - Carter: '76 and '70, 1970-1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alexander 1978 Reel (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Lew Lehrman Spots, Selected Reagan '84, New York Mayor, Governor, Misc., 1979-1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Lew Lehrman Spots, Lehrman Demo, Mario Cuomo-State of the State Address, Lehrman/Cuomo Debate, 10/07/1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    General note
    Note: This video also contains Mario Cuomo's State of the State address and a debate between Lehrman and Cuomo.
  - Alexander Reel, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Jack Lousma Compilation Reel, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Jim Dunn '84 Senate Primary, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Reagan/Bush Ads, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Includes: "Bear" and "Tax Vignettes."
  - Screening Reel for Joe Glick, 10/21/1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Includes: 1. Oil Spill, 2. Education, 3. Women, 4. Jobs, 5. ABC, 6. Jessica, 7. Choice, 8. Amanda, 9. Secret Plan, 10. Cuts, 11. Opinion, 12. Tear
  - Conrad, 10/28/1986 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Includes: "The Change We Need," "Burdick-Dorgan" and "Turnaround."
  - Dresner/Sykes, Hayden for Sykes, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Mark Andrews Spots, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Kent Conrad for Senate, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Includes: 1. For the Change We Need, 2. Bio, 3. Farm Prices, 4. Doubletalk, 5. Solutions, 6. Two Worlds, 7. Heigaard, 8. 2000, 9. Turnaround, 10. Their Friend, 11. Worth It
  - Payne & Company Political Demo Reel, 11/04/1987 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - AFL-CIO Convention, "People's Lobby", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - BCTD 1987 Legislative Conference, Grassroots Lobbying (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - BCTD "Get Out the Vote", 05/13/1988 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Campaign '88, 09/22/1988 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    National Education Association advertisements supporting Dukakis.
  - Presidential Campaign Commercial, 10/02/1988 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Doak and Shrum, 10/19/1988 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Don Ritter, "Hatchet Job", 11/01/1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Be in Good Company, Dough Wyles Production Inc. Sample Reel, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Rather/Bush, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Note: This advertisement is on the video in box 8 tape number 10. It contains an interview of George H.W. Bush by Dan Rather and Bush and Dukakis advertisements.
  - Coleman for Governor, #470 First Step, 09/21/1989 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Jim Courter Aired Spots, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Coleman for Governor, 1989 Primary Campaign (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Includes: America Looks, Considering, 20 Years, Marine, Department, Virginia Learns, Sean, Only One, Pay for It, Pledge, Character, Walked Away, Who Won't, Everywhere
  - Giuliani Commercials and other spots from the 89 cycle, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Friends of Giuliani, All Spots, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Tom Barrow Biography, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Joe Slade White, Greatest Hits, 02/12/1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - A City Divided, Jim Robinson for Supervisor, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - George Voinovich Compliation Reel, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Includes: GV-TV-01 "Best Decision," GV-TV-15 "Values," GV-TV-02 "Evening News," GV-TV-03 "Statement," GV-TV-20A "Real (Revised)," GV-TV-26 "The Fight," GV-TV-09 "What Kind of Man," GV-TV-38 "On Our Side"
  - Voinovich Environmental Footage, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Voinovich Ohio Story, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Voinovich Elements, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Voinovich "Elements", 1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Ohio Story Elements, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Voinovich Environmental, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Voinovich Columbus, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - George Voinovich All Abortion Reel, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Includes: GV-TV-03 "Statement," GV-TV-05 "Months of Thought," GV-TV-07 "Drum Beat," GV-TV-08 "Dates," GV-TV-09 "What Kind of Man," GV-TV-10 "Get Votes," GV-TV-11 "Papers," GV-TV-12 "Headlines," GV-TV-13 "Snap Shot," GV-TV-17 "Other Issues," GV-TV-18 "You'd Think," GV-TV-27 "Smarter," GV-TV-33 "Like You"
  - Various Bio Spots, 11/28/1990 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Includes: Gramm "Workin' & Winnin'," Danforth "Slide Show," Durenberger "Minn. Values," Giuliani "Bio," D'Amato "Ellis Island," Saxton "Drive," Dawkins "Bio," Bunning "This is Jim Bunning"
  - Dub of audio spots, Voinovich, 01/30/1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Michael P. Shea and Associates Demo Reel, 03/25/1991 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Includes: Vote No on Two "Fat Cats" "Weld/Silber," Ron Pina "Ron Pina vs Drug Smugglers," Kunin "Leadership" "Economy" "Garden" "Seasons," PIRGs "Earth Day 90," Joe Mackey "Street Smart," Carl Vivieros "Pride," Dukakis "Seabrook," "Record Hop."
  - St. Raymond Communication Demo Reel, 04/10/1991 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Rindy Media Demo Reel, 07/1991 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - "Barc", 08/1991 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Includes: 6 TV spots and 3 radio spots.
  - Baildr, "Gallagher Financial Systems", 09/19/1991 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Bob Lainer for Mayor Demo Reel, 12/09/1991 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Selected Spots from the 1991 Campaigns (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Includes: Campaign for Sensible Transportation ST-TV-04 "Triplet," John Lynch for State Senate JL-TV-01 "Combat," No on 553/Term Limits NO-R-03 "Danger," No on 553/Term Limits NO-TV-02 "Kansas"
  - Anti-Duke :30 Spots, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Includes: "Nazi," "General," "Newscast," "Duke on Tape," "Leaders," "Mayor," "Businessmen."
  - Ewe/Duke National 1991 Spots (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Struble-Totten Communications Demo Reel, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Elements for "Workin' and Winnin'", 01/09/1991 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - "Take Back America" Program, Brown for President, 01/22/1992 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Voinovich for Governor "Bandwagon", 02/13/1992 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - League of Conservation Voters "Greenscam-VA1", 03/03/1992 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Edmonds Powell Media Sample Reel, 03/1992 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Ruder-Finn Money Politics, 04/06/1992 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Labor Party Election Broadcast "Mandy" Version 1, 04/23/1992 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Note: video originally titled "Mandy."
  - Campaigns and Elections: Presidential Politics '92, 05/12/1992 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - The DLC-Leadership, 05/13/1992 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Fabrizio McLaughlin and Associates, 05/19/1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Note: video originally untitled.
  - "It's Time" and "All Together Now", 08/04/1992 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Perot Second Advertisement, 10/09/1992 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Perot Infomercials and ads from C-SPAN, 10/06/1992-10/17/1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - "Congress at the Crossroads," Perot advertisement, 10/26/1992 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Note: This advertisement is on the video in box 10 tape number 18. It contains the educational show "Congress at the Crossroads" and a biography of Ross Perot.
  - 1992 U.S. Presidential Campaign Commercials, 11/06/1992 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 1992 State/Local Campaign Commercials (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Lazlo Best of '92, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Inglis-A 1992 Campaign Presentation (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 1992 Demo Reel (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - 1992 Demo (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Includes: "Pothole" Ballot Proposition, "Bio" John Ray for Mayor, "Issues" Edwin Edwards for Governor, "Football" Edwin Edwards for Governor, "Titanic" Edwin Edwards for Governor, "Nazi" LA Democratic Party, "Jobs" Les Aspin Re-election, "Problem" I.E. vs Buddy Roemer, "Consumers" Bill Baxley for Governor, "Fox in the Hen House" Doug Schmidt for Secy. State, "Legacy" Ken Gibson for Governor, "Accomplishments" Sidney Barthelemy for Mayor, "Wild About Harry" Harry Lee for Sheriff, "Imagine" NEA, "Final Curtain" Edwin Edwards for Governor, "Jabberwocky" LA Coalition Against Racism and Nazism.
  - Spot Reel, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Demonstration Reel, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - "Presentation Reel", 02/08/1993 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Zakas for Senate and Wood for Representative, 04/16/1993 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Includes: Zakas for Senate "Commission" JZS-3001 and "Say Anything" JZS-3002, Wood for Representative "Committed" MWR-3001.
  - "Presentation Reel", 06/30/1993 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Only Cary Edwards Can Beat Jim Florio, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - 1993 Demo Reel (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Earle Williams for Governor, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Demo Reel, 01/1994 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - North for Senate "Candidates", 08/16/1994 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Branstad for Governor "Cop", 09/14/1994 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Engler for Governor "Linda", 10/03/1994 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Abraham for Senate "Ask Bill", 10/03/1994 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Haytaian for Senate "Red", 10/04/1994 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - North for Senate "Fiscal Issues", 10/06/1994 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Baldacci for Congress, 10/10/1994 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Includes: "Customer," "Dad's Words," and "Currier."
  - Fisher for Senate 94' "Pay and Play 2", 10/15/1994 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Elaine Baxter for Congress "Not This Time", 10/18/1994 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - L.F. Payne for Congress "Sold Out", 10/19/1994 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Bishop for Congress "So Many People", 10/27/1994 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - "Seniors", 11/01/1994 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Demo Reel "Victory 1994", 11/28/1994 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Tom Ridge for Governor "Tragic Mistake", 11/28/1994 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Jon Kyl for US Senate "On the Road", 11/28/1994 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Tom Ridge for Governor "Proud to Serve", 11/28/1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Jon Kyl for US Senate, 11/28/1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 1994 Demo Reel (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - The Best TV Spots: 1994 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Demo Reel '95, 04/20/1995 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Political Spots Reel, 08/18/1995 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - National Media, Inc. Spots, 08/21/1995 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Includes: Thompson for Senate (1994) "Hunt," "I Believe," "Runaround," "100 Counties"; Helms for Senate (1990) "Hands"; Beasley for Governor (1994) "Representing," "Honk"; Millner for Governor (1994) "Zell's Waltz."
  - 1995 TV Demo Reel (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Bob Dole: An American Hero, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - "Dreams", 12/12/1996 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Winning! Best Campaign Commercials of 1996 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - A Case Study of Congressman Maurice Hinchey's 1996 Campaign (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - 1996 Demo Reel (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - 1996 Demo Reel (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Lamspon for Congress "Case-Study", 1996 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Legislative Reel, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Presentation Reel, 04/01/1997 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    Includes: Kerry: President/Nursing-Alt/Battle, Toricelli: Brady/Endorse, Harkin: Heart/Frank, Reed: Hey Jack, Kennedy: Ahead/Message/Facts/Wage, Sarbanes: Bay/Clean up, Mikulski: Counting Wes, Wofford: Constitution/What Kind, Miller: Simpler/Not One/Quarter, Glover: Bio, DSCC GA: Guy, DSCC NH: Mister, DNC NJ: Stop, IA DP: Stand, ID DP: Ends.
  - Presentation Reel, 04/04/1997 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    Includes: Glenn: 102 Plane, 104 Advantage; Simon: 101 Bio, 305 Town, 205 National; Baliles: 108 Toxic Waste, 115 Walking, 123 Jobs; Robb: 206R Courage & Independence Revised, 112 R Education Revised, 401 Country; Cook: 101 Accomplishments, 105 Crackdown; Dinkins: 301 Young, 101 Bio, 104 Fields; Griego: 102 Cut Outs; Cranston: Adams; Walters: 203 Chambers, 350 Vision, 401 Sweep; Waihee: 201R Bio, 302 Literary; Skelton: Close to the People; Sarbanes: 101 Does; Kohl: 310 To the People, 106 Pound; Comparative & Response, Cranston: 725 Hits; Robb: 302 Deception, 964 Cooperated, 409 Account; Sarbanes: 302R Wait Revised; Dinkins: 112 Talk; Simon: 302 Compare; Cook: Excuse Me.
  - "The Democratic Party-America's Values for the 21st Century", 10/06/1997 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Demo Reel, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - 1997 Television Demo Reel (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - 1997 Demo Reel (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Jim McGreevy for Governor '97, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    Includes: "Priorities," "Education," "Insurance," "Two Democrats."
  - 1997 Demo Reel (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Demonstration Reel, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Matt Fong For U.S. Senate, 10/14/1998 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    Includes: "Abortion" and "Waste."
  - Matt Fong For U.S. Senate "Forest Compare", 10/20/1998 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Collin Peterson For Congress, 10/22/1998 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Includes: "Habitat," "Working Man," "Bailey," "Western Everywhere," "Shooting Star."
  - Ron Klink "Unjustifiable", 10/27/1998 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Davis and Vallone, 11/10/1998 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Includes: Davis: 110 Alone, 217 Apple, 233 San Diego; Vallone: 117 Stood.
  - Select :30 Spots, 11/23/1998 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Includes: David Dewhurst, Mike Johanns and Floridians for School Choice.
  - Favorites of 1998 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Includes: "Working" EM-TV-203 Ed McNamara, "Street" JG-TV-105 Jennifer Granholm, "Remarkable" MT-TV-101 Mike Thompson, "Shut" CPS-TC-102 Coloradans for Public Schools, "School" TK-TV-208 Tony Knowles, "Choose" TK-TV-207 Tony Knowles, "Diner" DH-TV-101 Dan Hynes, "Winter" DE-TV-101 Delaine Eastin, "Generations" MU-TV-102 Mark Udall, "Chauncy" MU-TV-115 Mark Udall.
  - Best of Compilation Reel 1998 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Lazlo & Associates, Inc., 1998 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 1998 Political Compilation (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Includes: "Our Home," "Golden Goose," "Alarming," "Search," "Broadcast News," "Scooter," "Save the Whales," "Invasion of the Nerds."
  - "Spot/Tumpel", 05/20/1999 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 1999 Demo Reel (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - 2000 Demo Reel (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Examples of Excellence Campaign 2000 Clips (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Lynn Yeakel for Senate, 05/05/2002 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Includes: "Here" #1, "Washington" #2, "My Vision" #5, "Truth" #6.
  - The Democratic Promise: Saul Alinsky & His Legacy (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Baldacci for Congress "Endorsement" (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - The World According to Robert Bork (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Note: This advertisement was produced by the Labor Institute of Public Affairs in opposition to Supreme Court nominee Robert Bork.
  - George Bush for President-Primary Spots (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Includes: "Free World Leadership," "Back Door Tax" (red parka), "Period" (straddle).
  - Jorge Carpo Spots/Footage (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Clinton II (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Includes: "A People United" and "Republican Revolution."
  - Kent Conrad (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Includes: "Two Worlds," "Clout" and "Other Candidate."
  - Kent Conrad "Heigaard" (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Crapo "Education" and Boozman "Veterans" (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - D'Amato Compilation Reels (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Dole Compilation Reel (Box 5, Folder 22)
    Includes: "Money" and "Qualities."
  - Bob Dole: To the Stars Through Difficulties (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Dukakis for President "President Quayle?" (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Dick Durbin for Senate (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Herschler for Congress "Cows" (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Tom Kean and Peter Shapiro (Box 5, Folder 27)
    Includes: Tom Kean "Remember?," Environment"; Peter Shapiro "Shake Things Up," "Spirit."
  - Dirk Kempthorne for Senate "Look Around" (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Kerrey and S. Levin (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Lehrman Demo (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Demo Reel for Jason Linde (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Sacia Debate LPW Ads (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Majic Demo (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Delegate Bob McDonnell (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Mark Neumann for Congress (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - North for Senate (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - People for O'Rourke (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Ross Perot, Bill Clinton Ads (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Van de Kamp Final Spot (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Van de Kamp Footage TC-1 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Van de Kamp Footage TC-2 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Van de Kamp Footage TC-3 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Van de Kamp Footage Selects and Music (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Voinovich and DeWine: An Ohio Story (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - George Voinovich: Compilation of Aired Spots (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Voinovich Stills (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Voinovich B-Roll of Columbus and Elements of Spots (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Voinovich Advertisement (Box 6, Folder 19)
    Note: video originally titled "White Rough Cut."
  - Original Time Code for Voinovich Rough Cut (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Comer Yates (Box 6, Folder 21)
    Includes: CY-01 Citizen Yates w/ Tag and CY-02 Why Not? w/ Tag.
  - Comer Yates "Peanuts" (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - America's Largest Republican Meeting (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Arizona Consumer Insurance Coalition (Box 6, Folder 24)
    Includes: No on 201, People for Fair Insurance, Billboard; No on 201, People for Fair Insurance, Blackboard; Yes on 201, Arizona Policyholders Association, Powell; Yes on 201, Arizona Policyholders Association, Rolling Words; No on 105, Arizona Alert, Ralph Nader; News, 201 Lawsuit Coverage; News, KAET Opinion Survey/Powell Commentary (as Policyholders Association); News, Harvey Rosenfeld Press Coverage; News, Richard Weibe/AC/IC Telephone Bank. Note: This Video also contains news reports compiled by the Arizona Consumer Insurance Coalition.
  - Campaign Spots (Box 6, Folder 25)
    Advertisement produced by Howard N. Mead & Company.
  - CBS Image Promos (Box 6, Folder 26)
    Note: This video also contains a local news report.
  - Child Pornography Spots (Box 6, Folder 27)
    Advertisement produced by The Media Team. Includes: Voinovich "Make Us Wait," Voinovich "Bare Bones," Metzenbaum "Think," Celebrezze "Porn."
  - Challengers/Open Seats (Box 6, Folder 28)
    Advertisement produced by The Campaign Group.
  - Congressional Campaigns (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Corporate Video Presentation (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Advertisement produced by Fabrizio, McLaughlin & Associates, Inc.
  - Demo Tape (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Advertisement produced by Al Rothstein Media Services, Inc.
  - Demo Reel I (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Advertisement produced by Austin/Sheinkopf.
  - Demo Reel (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Demo Reel (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Demo Reel (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Advertisement produced by The Campaign Group. Includes: Pickle "Skyline" 1986, Goode "Growing Up" 1983, Kennelly "Intelligence" 1990, Gore "The Hill" 1988, Abramson "Special" 1989, Bullock "Menu" 1990, Sharp "Car" 1990, Kennelly "Infant" 1988, Hefner "School" 1990, Loftus "Unfair" 1990, Blumenthal "Crime" 1990, Neal "Environment" 1990, Gore "Lop Sided" 1988, Gore "Debate" 1988, Bullock "Environment" 1990, Bullock "Children" 1990, Patterson "Newspaper" 1990, Loftus "Crime" 1990, Borski "Interested" 1982, Sharp "Trouble" 1990, Smith "Effective" 1990, Neal "Laws" 1988, Hoeffel "Junket" 1986, Goode "Umbrellas" 1983.
  - Demonstration Reel (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Advertisement produced by McKinnon Media.
  - Demo Reel (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Advertisement produced by The Media Team.
  - Demonstration Reel (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Advertisement produced by Strother-Duffy-Strother.
  - First Spot (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Advertisement produced by The Image Maker.
  - Greatest Hits (Box 7, Folder 12)
    Advertisement produced by Axelrod and Associates
  - Humorous Ads (Revised) (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Maryland Committee Against the Gun Bans Commercial (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - The New Inexpensive Alternative to Television! (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Advertisement produced by Political Video Duplicators.
  - Newspapers-The Strategic Medium (Box 7, Folder 16)
    Advertisement produced by Newspaper Associate of America.
  - Nixon Speeches, "Republican Leadership at the Grassroots," RNC 1980 Spots (Box 7, Folder 17)